fendt.com 2018-08-29

# Privacy Policy | Imprint - AGCO GmbH

We are pleased that you are visiting our websites and about your interest in our company. The protection of your personal data is of considerable importance to us. Personal data are individual details about personal or factual circumstances of a certain or definable natural person. This includes e.g. information such as the civilian name, the address, the telephone number and the date of birth.

As personal data enjoy special protection, they are only collected. Processed and used in our company to the admissible extent. We will explain this in more detail to you below.

 **1\. Responsible party**

The responsible party within the meaning of Art. 4 Para. 7 EU-General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) is:

AGCO GmbH  
Johann-Georg-Fendt-Straße 4  
D-87616 Marktoberdorf  
E-mail: info.fendt@agcocorp.com   
Phone: +49 (0)8342 / 77-0  
Fax: +49 (0)8342 / 77-220

You can contact our data protection officer per e-mail under [**DataPrivacy@agcocorp.com**](mailto:DataPrivacy@agcocorp.com) or by post via our postal address with the supplement “the data protection officer”.

 **2\. Automatic data collection and processing by the browser**

You can principally visit our websites without entering any personal data. As with each website our server automatically and temporarily collected details in the server logfiles, which are transmitted by the browser if this was not deactivated by you. If you would like to view our website, we collect the following data, which are necessary for us from a technical point of view in order to display our website to you and to guarantee the stability and security (the legal basis is Art. 6 Para. 1 S. 1 lit. f GDPR):

  * IP address  

  * Date and time of the enquiry  

  * Time zone difference to Greenwich Mean Time (GMT)  

  * Contents of the requirement (concrete site)  

  * Access status /HTTP-status code  

  * respectively transmitted data volume  

  * Website, from which the requirement comes  

  * Browser  

  * Operating system and its interface  

  * Language and version of the browser software.  

 **3\. Special functions of the websites**

Our websites offer you various functions with the use of which personal data are collected, processed and used. We will explain to you below what happens with these data:

 **Newsletter:**

The data entered by the user in the registration mask of our newsletter will be exclusively used by us for the sending of our newsletter, in which we inform about all of our services. We will send you a confirmation e-mail after the registration that contains a link, which you must click in order to conclude the registration to our newsletter (Double-Opt-In). . After your confirmation we will store your entered data for the purpose of sending the newsletter (the legal basis is Art. 6 Para. 1 S. 1 lit. a GDPR).The newsletter can be unsubscribed to at all times by clicking on the unsubscribe-links.

We would like to point out to you that we evaluate your user behaviour when sending the newsletter. For this evaluation the sent e-mails contain so-called tracking pixel, which represent a one-pixel image files. For the evaluations we link the data stated in Subclause 2 and the tracking pixel with an individual ID. With the thus gained data we create a user profile in order to customise the newsletter to meet your individual interests. We enter hereby when and where (based on your IP address) you read our newsletter and conclude from this how we can improve our newsletter for you.

Such a tracking is moreover not possible if you have deactivated the display of images as a standard in your e-mail programme. In this case the newsletter will not be displayed to you in full and you may not be able to use all functions. If you have the images displayed manually, the aforementioned tracking will be carried out.

 **Contact form:**

We will only use the data entered by the user via our contact form for the processing of enquiries, which are received via the contact form (the legal basis is Art. 6 Para. 1 S. 1 lit. b GDPR). After the final processing of the enquiry the collected data will be deleted without delay insofar as there are no statutory storage deadlines.

 **Career – application (online application):**

The data collected within the scope of the online application by entry of the user exclusively serve the possible substantiation of an employment relationship and will be processed or used earmarked. With the input of your data you declare that you agree with the processing and use of your data by the following legal entities:

  * AGCO GmbH, Johann-Georg-Fendt-Straße 4, D-87616 Marktoberdorf  

  * AGCO Deutschland GmbH, Johann-Georg-Fendt-Straße 14, D-87616 Marktoberdorf  

(the legal basis for the forwarding and processing of your application is your consent)

 **Fendt vehicle configurator:**

By using the Fendt vehicle configurator, you have the possibility to configure various Fendt vehicles and to store these configurations online. You have the possibility hereby to call your configurations once again at a later time.

A registration is necessary in order to use this function. It is obligatory to enter an e-mail address in this respect. Further personal data can be entered and subsequently changed, are however optional. After the registration a password will be sent to the user to the entered e-mail address (the legal basis is Art. 6 Para. 1 S. 1 lit. b GDPR).

If you should have forgotten your password for the Fendt vehicle configurator, there is the possibility to have this sent to you once again via the function “have you forgotten your password”. For this purpose, it is necessary to enter the e-mail address, with which you have registered for the Fendt vehicle configurator.

The data, which are collected within the scope of the function 'have you forgotten your password', will only be used for the renewed sending of forgotten passwords.

 **4\. Data transfer / specified purpose**

We only forward personal data to third parties insofar as this is necessary for us in order to fulfil our contractual obligations, in particular to process a concluded contract. With the provision of our website we also forward your data to the service providers commissioned in this respect (e.g. hosting partner, agency, etc.), which exclusively process the personal data by order and following instructions from us. A forwarding of personal data to third parties does not take place except for the stated purposes of the contractual and payment processing or only with your consent.

If you make personal data available to us within the scope of an enquiry or owing to an explicit consent, these data are only used for the purpose, which is covered by the enquiry or the consent. With your consent and in order to fulfil the purpose your personal data can be forwarded within the [**AGCO Group**](http://www.agcocorp.com/contact/facilities-list.html) and also to regional distribution partners. You can request the distribution partners that are responsible for your region yourself at all times via the following link [**www.fendt.com/Händlersuche**](https://www.fendt.com/int/11801.html) (dealer search) or request this from us.

We will only store your personal data for as long as this is necessary or stipulated by law for the envisaged purpose of the data collection. You can revoke your consent at all times. Your interests that are worthy of protection will be taken into consideration pursuant to the statutory provisions. If data recipients are located in countries outside of the European Economic Area (EEA), in which the applicable law does not guarantee the same standard of data protection as in your home country, we will take measures in order to ensure an appropriate standard of data protection otherwise.

You can also find further information pertaining to the data protection within the [**AGCO Group**](http://www.agcocorp.com/contact/facilities-list.html) from our general [Privacy-Policy](http://www.agcocorp.com/privacy.html).

 **5\. Statistical evaluation of the visits to our websites**

We will also use the data transmitted by your web browser pursuant to Subclause 2 for the consistent improvement of our internet offer and for statistical purposes.

 **Google-Analytics:**

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service of Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses so-called “cookies”, text files, which are stored on your computer and which enable an analysis of the use of the website by you. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is as a rule transmitted to a server of Google in the USA and is stored there. In the event of the activation of the IP anonymisation on this website, your IP address is however previously abbreviated by Google within member states of the European Union or in other contracting states of the Treaty on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be transmitted to a server of Google in the USA and will be abbreviated there. BY order of the operator of this website Google will use this information in order to evaluate your use of the website in order to compile reports about the website activities and in order to provide further services associated with the website use and the internet use towards the website operator.

The IP address transmitted within the scope of Google Analytics from your browser will not be aggregated with other data of Google according to the statements of Google.

You can prevent the storage of the cookies by a corresponding setting of your browser software, we would like to point out to you however that in this case you will, if applicable, not be able to use all functions of this website in full. You can additionally prevent the entry of the data generated by the cookie and which refers to your use of the website (incl. your IP address) to Google as well as the processing of these data by Google by downloading and installing the browser plugin available under the following link -: [**https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en**](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).

This website uses Google Analytics with the extension “_anonymizeIp()”. This way your IP addresses will be abbreviated and further processed, an ability to make reference to a person can thus be excluded. Insofar as the data collected in relation to you has a reference to a person, this will thus be excluded immediately, and the personal data will therefore be deleted immediately.

We use Google Analytics in order to be able to analyse and regularly improve the use of our website. Via the gained statistics we can improve our offer and design is more interesting for you as a user. For the exceptional cases, in which personal data are transmitted to the USA, Google has submitted itself to the EU-US Privacy Shield, [**https://www.privacyshield.gov/EU-US-Framework**](https://www.privacyshield.gov/EU-US-Framework). The legal basis for the use of Google Analytics is Art. 6 Para. 1 S. 1 lit. f GDPR.

Information of the third-party provider: Google Dublin, Google Ireland Ltd., Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland, Fax: +353 (1) 436 1001. Conditions of use: [**https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/**](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/), overview of data protection: [**https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en**](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en), as well as the privacy statement: **  

 **etracker:**

By using technologies of etracker GmbH ([ **http://www.etracker.com**](http://www.etracker.com/)) data are collected and stored for marketing and optimisation purposes on this website. Usage profiles can be created from these data under pseudonym. Cookies can be used for this purpose. Cookies are small text files, which are stored locally in the cache of the internet browser of the site visitor. The cookies enable the recognition of the internet browser. The data collected using the eTracker-Technologies are not used without the separately granted consent of the data subject in order to personally identify the visitor of this website and will not be aggregated with personal data about the holder of the pseudonym. The data collection and storage can be objected to at all times with effect for the future.

Please exclude me from the eTracker counting. 

We use eTracker in order to be able to analyse and regularly improve the use of our website. Via the gained statistics we can improve our offer and design is more interesting for you as a user. The collected data will be stored permanently and analysed using pseudonyms. The legal basis for the use of eTracker is Art. 6 Para. 1 S. 1 lit. f GDPR.  

Information of the third-party provider: etracker GmbH, Erste Brunnenstraße 1, 20459 Hamburg; [**https://www.etracker.com/en/data-privacy/**](https://www.etracker.com/en/data-privacy/). The legal basis for the use of eTracker is Art. 6 Para. 1 S. 1 lit. f GDPR.

 **6\. External contents**

Simple links to Social Media operators

Our websites make simple links available to websites of the operator of Social Media. A data exchange with the Social Media operators will only take place if you click on the button with the symbol (e.g. the “f” of Facebook). If you click on such a button, a site of the Social Media operator opens in a PopUp window and you will thus find yourself on the websites of the respective Social Media operator. The provisions of the respective Social Media operator apply.

 **Social plugins, Social Media offers**

On our websites so-called Social Plugins or contents of the following social networks are used or integrated (hereinafter the “social networks”). We moreover maintain online presences within social networks and platforms in order to communicate with the customers active there, interested parties and users and to be able to inform them there about our services. When calling the respective networks and platforms the Business Terms and Conditions and the privacy policies of their respective operator shall apply.

Insofar as not otherwise stated within the scope of our privacy statement, we process the data of the users if these communicate with us within the social networks and platforms, e.g. write contributions on our online presences or to send us messages. Incidentally, the following specific notices apply:

 **Facebook:**

We use the Social Graph and further integrations of Facebook (“Facebook Plugins”) of Facebook Inc., 1601 Willow Road, Menlo Park, California, 94025, USA (“Facebook”), which connects this website with the social network of Facebook in order to present contents of Facebook on our site. Further information about the function and appearance of the Facebook Plugins can be found under [**http://developers.facebook.com/plugins**](http://developers.facebook.com/plugins).

With the activation (see Subclause 4.2) of the Facebook Plugins your browser establishes a direct connection with the servers of Facebook. The contents of Facebook Plugins will be transmitted directly by Facebook to your browser. At the same time certain data will be transmitted by your browser to Facebook. This takes place irrespective of whether you click on the Facebook Plugins or not. We have no influence on the volume of the data, which Facebook collects in this manner. According to our current status of knowledge it concerns the following data:

  * visited page on our website, which contains the Facebook Plugin,  

  * the general data transmitted by your browser (IP address, browser type and version, operating system, time),  

  * with registered Facebook users, the respective Facebook-identification number.  

For the purpose and scope of the data collection and the further processing and use of the data by Facebook as well as your rights in this respect and setting possibilities for the protection of your privacy please refer to the data protection notices of Facebook: [**http://www.facebook.com/policy.php**](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php). You are entitled to a right of objection against the formation of possible user profiles, whereby you must contact Facebook in order to assert these rights The legal basis for the use of the Facebook Plugin is Art. 6 Para. 1 S. 1 lit. f GDPR.

If you are a member of Facebook and would not like Facebook to collect data about you via our website and to link these with your member data stored at Facebook, you must log out of Facebook before your visit to our internet presence and delete possibly existing cookies of Facebook. The Facebook Plugins can in addition be blocked with the help of Add-Ons for the own browser. Further information in this respect can be found on the Add-On sites of the browser.

 **YouTube:**

For the presentation of our videos we use the video service of YouTube, LLC, 901 Cherry Ave., San Bruno, CA 94066, USA (“YouTube”).

In order to guarantee an as far as possible comprehensive protection of your data we use technical solutions, so that a data transfer to YouTube is only carried out after the prior activation by you. Only after you activate these deactivated plugins, by clicking on our website the button “activate Social Media”, will you thus declare your consent to the transmission of the data determined below to YouTube. With a further click you can then e.g. start a video, send a recommendation within the respective social network etc. If you are already logged into a social network during the use of our websites, as a rule no further log-in dialogue will be displayed.

 **With the clicking on the button “activate Social Media” you grant your consent to the fact that the data determined subsequently are transmitted to YouTube.**

 **You can revoke your consent for the future at all times by a click on the button “deactivate Social Media”.**

If YouTube-videos have been entered on our website and you have activated YouTube as previously described, the content of the entered video will be transmitted by YouTube directly to your browser. At the same time certain data are transmitted from your browser to YouTube. This takes place irrespective whether you click on the video or not. The legal basis for the use of Youtube is Art. 6 Para. 1 S. 1 lit. f GDPR. We have no influence on the volume of the data, which YouTube collects on this website. According to our current status of knowledge it concerns the following data, in particular relating to the presentation of the entered YouTube videos:

  * Visited site on our website, which contains the video,  

  * The general data transmitted by your browser (IP address, browser type and -version, operation system, time)  

  * With registered Youtube- or Google-users, your Google-user identifier.  

Embedded YouTube videos can also be faded out by browser Add-Ons so that no data collection takes place by YouTube.

 **Google Maps:**

On this website we use the offer Google Maps. This way we can display interactive maps to you directly in the website and enable you the comfortable use of the maps function.

By the visit to the website Google receives the information that you have called the corresponding sub-site of our website. Moreover, the data stated under Subclause 2 of this statement are transmitted. This is carried out irrespective whether Google makes a user account available, via which you are logged in, or whether no user account exists. If you are logged into Google your data will be allocated directly to the account. If you do not request the allocation with your profile at Google you must log out before activating the button. Google stores your data as a usage profile and uses these for the purpose of advertising, market research and/or a design of our website more suitable for the needs. Such an evaluation is carried out in particular (even for users that are not logged in) to provide advertising suitable for the needs and in order to inform other users of the social network about your activities on our website. You are entitled to a right of objection against the formation of this user profile, whereby you must contact Google directly in order to assert this right.

You can find further information relating to purposes and scope of the data collection and their processing by the plugin-provider in the privacy statements of the provider. There you can also obtain further information relating to your rights in this respect and setting possibilities relating to the protection of your privacy: [**https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en**](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en). Google also processes your personal data in the USA and has submitted itself to the EU-US Privacy Shield, [**https://www.privacyshield.gov/EU-US-Framework**](https://www.privacyshield.gov/EU-US-Framework). The legal basis for the use of Google Maps is Art. 6 Para. 1 S. 1 lit. f GDPR.

 **Instagram:**

Within our online offer functions and contents of the Instagram service are embedded, offered and by Instagram Inc., 1601 Willow Road, Menlo Park, CA, 94025, USA. For this purpose, you can e.g. enter contents including as photos, videos or texts and buttons, with which users can show that they like these relating to the contents the writer of the contents or can subscribe to our contributions. If the users are members of the platform Instagram, Instagram can allocate the call of the aforementioned contents and functions to the profiles of the users therein. Privacy statement of Instagram: [**http://instagram.com/about/legal/privacy/**](https://help.instagram.com/155833707900388).

 **Whatsapp:**

If you subscribe to our Fendt Whatsapp Newsfeed, we will process your mobile phone number exclusively within the scope of your consent, which you grant us with the subscription of the Fendt-Newsfeed via the sending of the word “START”. You can revoke your consent at all times by sending the word “STOP” to the Whatsapp-Newsfeed. Within the scope of the Whatsapp-Newsfeed your mobile phone number will be collected and processed by our technical service provider WhatsBroadcast GmbH. A processing is exclusively carried out within the scope of the consent granted by you with the subscription. It will exclusively use these data to service the messenger service and to send our contributions. It will not evaluate these data. WhatsBroadcast GmbH is an independent German service provider and does not belong to the WhatsApp-Group. For further information please refer to the privacy statement of Whatsbroadcast under [**https://www.whatsbroadcast.com/de/datenschutz/**](https://www.whatsbroadcast.com/de/datenschutz/).

In this context your telephone number will also be transmitted to WhatsApp, Inc and linked with your Whatsapp account. Further information can be derived from the privacy statement of Whatsapp: **[https://www.whatsapp.com/legal/#terms-of-service](https://www.whatsapp.com/legal/?lang=en) **The transmission is carried out exclusively for the subscription to and use of our Fendt Whatsapp-Newsfeed

 **Further external contents:**

 **Adobe Typekit:**

On our websites we use the font “Myriad pro” from the “Adobe Typekit” of the company Adobe Systems Incorporated, 345 Park Ave, San Jose, CA 95110, USA. Over the course of the provision of the Typekit service **no cookies** are placed or used in order make the font available. The legal basis for the use of Adobe Typekit is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f GDPR.

The following information is entered by Adobe to provide the Typekit service:

In order to provide the Typekit-service Adobe can enter information about the fonts, which are made available on our server. The information is used for the settlement and compliance with regulations and can comprise the following:

  * Font that is made available  

  * ID of the set  

  * Account -ID  

  * Service, which makes fonts available (e.g. Typekit or Edge Web Fonts)  

  * Application, which requests the fonts (e.g. Adobe Muse)  

  * Server, which makes the fonts available (e.g. Typekit-Server or Enterprise CDN)  

  * Host name of the site, on which the fonts are loaded  

  * The time, which the Webbrowser needs for downloading fonts  

  * The time from the downloading of the fonts with the Webbrowser until the application of the fonts  

You can call further information relating to the data protection provisions of the tool under the following link: [**https://www.adobe.com/uk/privacy/policies/typekit.html**](https://www.adobe.com/uk/privacy/policies/typekit.html)

 **7\. Notification about the use of cookies**

On our websites we partly use cookies in order to design the visit to our website more attractive and to enable the use of certain functions. You can set your browser yourself according to your wishes to the extent that you are informed about the setting of cookies, from case to case decide about the acceptance or the principally accept cookies or principally excluded these. Cookies can be used for different purposes, e.g. in order to recognise that your PC had a connection to an internet offer once before already (permanent cookies) or in order store last viewed offers (session cookies). We use cookies in order to offer you a better user comfort. In order to use our comfort functions, we recommend that you allow the acceptance of cookies for our internet offer. You can call more detailed information pertaining to our cookie policy under the following link: [**http://www.agcocorp.com/cookies.html**](http://www.agcocorp.com/cookies.html)

 **8\. Data security and data protection, communication per e-mail**

Your personal data are stored by taking all technical and organisational possibilities so that they are not accessible for third parties. With the communication per e-mail the full data security cannot be guaranteed by us so that we recommend that you use the normal postal service with information with a high need for secrecy.

 **9\. Your rights**

You have the following rights towards us with regard to personal data relating to you:

  * Right to information,  

  * Right to rectification or deletion,  

  * Right to limitation of the processing,  

  * Right to file an objection against the processing,  

  * Right to data portability.  

Please send your written enquiries to our contact possibilities stated at the beginning.

You have moreover the right to complain at a data protection supervisory authority about the processing of your personal data by us.

This privacy statement is adjusted from time to time. (Status: 25 May 2018)
